[{"answer_ne_tagged": {"DATE": ["Sunday"], "LOCATION": ["Joplin"]}, "docId": "110524pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NN", ",", "RB", "IN", "DT", "NN", ",", "CC", "IN", "NNP", "IN", "NNP", ",", "VBZ", "."], "qSentId": 65, "question": "Is that right?", "question_tokens": ["Is", "that", "right", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["VBZ", "IN", "JJ", "."], "aSentId": 66, "answer": "Today, not in that situation, but in Joplin on Sunday, yes.", "answer_tokens": ["Today", ",", "not", "in", "that", "situation", ",", "but", "in", "Joplin", "on", "Sunday", ",", "yes", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110524pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBZ", "JJ", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 74, "question": "How bad is this situation that's now enveloping this region?", "question_tokens": ["How", "bad", "is", "this", "situation", "that", "'s", "now", "enveloping", "this", "region", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "JJ", "VBZ", "DT", "NN", "IN", "POS", "RB", "VBG", "DT", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 75, "answer": "It's bad today.", "answer_tokens": ["It", "'s", "bad", "today", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"ORGANIZATION": ["Piers"]}, "docId": "110524pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "NN", ",", "NNP", "."], "qSentId": 88, "question": "Sam, what's the latest?", "question_tokens": ["Sam", ",", "what", "'s", "the", "latest", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "WP", "VBZ", "DT", "JJS", "."], "aSentId": 89, "answer": "Good evening, Piers.", "answer_tokens": ["Good", "evening", ",", "Piers", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110524pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "RB", "VBP", "RB", "."], "qSentId": 111, "question": "Do you have any clue as to where he may be?", "question_tokens": ["Do", "you", "have", "any", "clue", "as", "to", "where", "he", "may", "be", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VB", "DT", "NN", "IN", "TO", "WRB", "PRP", "MD", "VB", "."], "aSentId": 112, "answer": "We really don't.", "answer_tokens": ["We", "really", "do", "n't", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110524pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "IN", "RB", "WDT", "PRP", "VBD", "IN", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "NN", "NN", ",", "IN", "PRP", "MD", "RB", "VB", "WRB", "PRP", "VBD", "VBG", "."], "qSentId": 118, "question": "What do you think may have happened?", "question_tokens": ["What", "do", "you", "think", "may", "have", "happened", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", "MD", "VB", "VBN", "."], "aSentId": 119, "answer": "I mean, we know for sure that they pulled into that grocery store parking lot, because they couldn't see where they were going.", "answer_tokens": ["I", "mean", ",", "we", "know", "for", "sure", "that", "they", "pulled", "into", "that", "grocery", "store", "parking", "lot", ",", "because", "they", "could", "n't", "see", "where", "they", "were", "going", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"LOCATION": ["Wisconsin"]}, "docId": "110524pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "JJ", ",", "IN", "JJ", "CC", "NNP", "VBZ", "DT", "NN", "WRB", "DT", "NN", "VBD", ":"], "qSentId": 137, "question": "On 20th Street?", "question_tokens": ["On", "20th", "Street", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["IN", "JJ", "NNP", "."], "aSentId": 138, "answer": "I'm sorry, on 20th and Wisconsin is the corner where the car was --", "answer_tokens": ["I", "'m", "sorry", ",", "on", "20th", "and", "Wisconsin", "is", "the", "corner", "where", "the", "car", "was", "--"], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110524pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", ":", "RB", ",", "RB", "PRP$", "JJ", "NN", "VBD", "RB", "IN", "DT", "NNS", "VBG", "CC", "IN", "VBZ", "PRP", "."], "qSentId": 141, "question": "And Lantz's friend is Jonathan Taylor, and his last memory is that he may be still alive, he thinks?", "question_tokens": ["And", "Lantz", "'s", "friend", "is", "Jonathan", "Taylor", ",", "and", "his", "last", "memory", "is", "that", "he", "may", "be", "still", "alive", ",", "he", "thinks", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["CC", "NNP", "POS", "NN", "VBZ", "NNP", "NNP", ",", "CC", "PRP$", "JJ", "NN", "VBZ", "IN", "PRP", "MD", "VB", "RB", "JJ", ",", "PRP", "VBZ", "."], "aSentId": 142, "answer": "No -- well, really his last memory was just of the windows breaking and that's it.", "answer_tokens": ["No", "--", "well", ",", "really", "his", "last", "memory", "was", "just", "of", "the", "windows", "breaking", "and", "that", "'s", "it", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Lantz", "Jonathan Taylor"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110524pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBZ", "VBN", "."], "qSentId": 252, "question": "Is it completely gone?", "question_tokens": ["Is", "it", "completely", "gone", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["VBZ", "PRP", "RB", "VBN", "."], "aSentId": 253, "answer": "It's gone.", "answer_tokens": ["It", "'s", "gone", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110524pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBZ", "RB", "VBG", "."], "qSentId": 317, "question": "How do you feel?", "question_tokens": ["How", "do", "you", "feel", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", "."], "aSentId": 318, "answer": "It's pretty terrifying.", "answer_tokens": ["It", "'s", "pretty", "terrifying", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110524pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP$", "NN", "RB", "RB", "VBD", ",", "IN", ",", "PRP", "VBP", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "VBN", "EX", "IN", "CD", "NNS", "."], "qSentId": 325, "question": "Elizabeth, when you saw the pictures of the school, what went through your mind?", "question_tokens": ["Elizabeth", ",", "when", "you", "saw", "the", "pictures", "of", "the", "school", ",", "what", "went", "through", "your", "mind", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "WRB", "PRP", "VBD", "DT", "NNS", "IN", "DT", "NN", ",", "WP", "VBD", "IN", "PRP$", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 326, "answer": "My heart pretty much stopped, because, I mean, we've gone there for four years.", "answer_tokens": ["My", "heart", "pretty", "much", "stopped", ",", "because", ",", "I", "mean", ",", "we", "'ve", "gone", "there", "for", "four", "years", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110524pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "RB", "IN", "PRP", "VBD", "TO", "VB", "NN", "PRP$", "NNS", ",", "CD", "IN", "PRP$", "JJ", "NN", "RB", "VBD", "IN", "EX", "VBD", "DT", "NN", "NN", ",", "CC", "IN", "NN", "MD", "VB", "JJ", "CC", "PRP", "VBD", ":", "PRP", "VBD", "RB", "VBG", "PRP", "TO", "VB", "NN", "IN", "DT", "NN", "CC", "IN", "PRP", "VBD", "VBG", "TO", "VB", "RB", ",", "TO", "VB", "RB", "RB", "."], "qSentId": 330, "question": "When did you become aware about what was happening?", "question_tokens": ["When", "did", "you", "become", "aware", "about", "what", "was", "happening", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "VBD", "PRP", "VB", "JJ", "IN", "WP", "VBD", "VBG", "."], "aSentId": 331, "answer": "Well, shortly after we had to go get our diplomas, one of our senior principal actually said that there was a tornado watch, and that everyone should be careful and he was -- he was just telling us to keep check on the weather and if we were going to go home, to go home directly.", "answer_tokens": ["Well", ",", "shortly", "after", "we", "had", "to", "go", "get", "our", "diplomas", ",", "one", "of", "our", "senior", "principal", "actually", "said", "that", "there", "was", "a", "tornado", "watch", ",", "and", "that", "everyone", "should", "be", "careful", "and", "he", "was", "--", "he", "was", "just", "telling", "us", "to", "keep", "check", "on", "the", "weather", "and", "if", "we", "were", "going", "to", "go", "home", ",", "to", "go", "home", "directly", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110524pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["RB", ",", "PRP", "VBD", "PRP", "IN", "DT", ",", "NN", ",", "RB", ",", "PRP", "VBZ", "DT", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 335, "question": "Did you see it as real, or did it all just seem like, oh, well, it's just another warning?", "question_tokens": ["Did", "you", "see", "it", "as", "real", ",", "or", "did", "it", "all", "just", "seem", "like", ",", "oh", ",", "well", ",", "it", "'s", "just", "another", "warning", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VB", "PRP", "IN", "JJ", ",", "CC", "VBD", "PRP", "RB", "RB", "VBP", "IN", ",", "JJ", ",", "RB", ",", "PRP", "VBZ", "RB", "DT", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 336, "answer": "Frankly, I took it as another, oh, well, it's another warning.", "answer_tokens": ["Frankly", ",", "I", "took", "it", "as", "another", ",", "oh", ",", "well", ",", "it", "'s", "another", "warning", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"ORGANIZATION": ["Ozark Christian College"], "LOCATION": ["Joplin"]}, "docId": "110524pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "VBG", "TO", "NNP", "NNP", "NNP", "RB", "IN", "NNP", ",", "CC", "PRP", "VBD", "RB", "VB", "VBN", "IN", "DT", "NN", "IN", "DT", ",", "IN", "PRP", "VBZ", "IN", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "IN", "NNP", "."], "qSentId": 339, "question": "Do you know what you're going to be doing?", "question_tokens": ["Do", "you", "know", "what", "you", "'re", "going", "to", "be", "doing", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VB", "WP", "PRP", "VBP", "VBG", "TO", "VB", "VBG", "."], "aSentId": 340, "answer": "I'm going to Ozark Christian College here at Joplin, and it didn't get affected by the tornado at all, because it's on the north end of Joplin.", "answer_tokens": ["I", "'m", "going", "to", "Ozark", "Christian", "College", "here", "at", "Joplin", ",", "and", "it", "did", "n't", "get", "affected", "by", "the", "tornado", "at", "all", ",", "because", "it", "'s", "on", "the", "north", "end", "of", "Joplin", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Joplin"], "LOCATION": ["Joplin"]}, "docId": "110524pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "DT", "NN", "IN", "PRP", "VBP", "IN", "NN", ",", "IN", "PRP", "VBP", "RB", "VBN", ",", "IN", ",", "JJ", ",", "NNP", "VBZ", "RB", "DT", "NN", "WRB", "DT", "NN", "VBZ", "CC", "PRP", "VBP", "RB", "VBN", "IN", ",", "JJ", ",", "NN", "RB", "VBZ", "IN", "NNP", "."], "qSentId": 347, "question": "How would you describe the mood?", "question_tokens": ["How", "would", "you", "describe", "the", "mood", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "MD", "PRP", "VB", "DT", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 348, "answer": "Well, a lot of us are in shock, because we've always been, like, oh, Joplin is always the place where the tornado misses or we've always been like, oh, nothing ever happens in Joplin.", "answer_tokens": ["Well", ",", "a", "lot", "of", "us", "are", "in", "shock", ",", "because", "we", "'ve", "always", "been", ",", "like", ",", "oh", ",", "Joplin", "is", "always", "the", "place", "where", "the", "tornado", "misses", "or", "we", "'ve", "always", "been", "like", ",", "oh", ",", "nothing", "ever", "happens", "in", "Joplin", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110524pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBZ", "."], "qSentId": 353, "question": "It's heartbreaking, isn't it?", "question_tokens": ["It", "'s", "heartbreaking", ",", "is", "n't", "it", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBZ", "VBG", ",", "VBZ", "RB", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 354, "answer": "It is.", "answer_tokens": ["It", "is", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110524pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "IN", "PRP", "MD", "VB", "IN", "IN", "PRP", "."], "qSentId": 412, "question": "Piers?", "question_tokens": ["Piers", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNS", "."], "aSentId": 413, "answer": "Rob, if you can stand by for us.", "answer_tokens": ["Rob", ",", "if", "you", "can", "stand", "by", "for", "us", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"ORGANIZATION": ["Piers"], "LOCATION": ["Alabama"]}, "docId": "110524pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "NNP", ",", "PRP", "MD", "VB", "PRP", ",", "PRP", "RB", "VBD", "RP", "IN", "NNP", ",", "PRP", "VBZ", "IN", "NN", ",", "CC", "PRP", "RB", "VBZ", "TO", "VB", "PRP", ",", "DT", "NN", "VBZ", "RB", "JJ", "."], "qSentId": 424, "question": "Given other scenes you've had to go and help at, how does this rank?", "question_tokens": ["Given", "other", "scenes", "you", "'ve", "had", "to", "go", "and", "help", "at", ",", "how", "does", "this", "rank", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["RB", "JJ", "NNS", "PRP", "VBP", "VBN", "TO", "VB", "CC", "VB", "IN", ",", "WRB", "VBZ", "DT", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 425, "answer": "Well, Piers, I can tell you, I just got back from Alabama, it seems like yesterday, and it never ceases to amaze me, the destruction is just epic.", "answer_tokens": ["Well", ",", "Piers", ",", "I", "can", "tell", "you", ",", "I", "just", "got", "back", "from", "Alabama", ",", "it", "seems", "like", "yesterday", ",", "and", "it", "never", "ceases", "to", "amaze", "me", ",", "the", "destruction", "is", "just", "epic", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110524pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "VB", "PRP", ",", "JJ", "IN", "DT", ",", "VBP", "RB", "CC", "VB", "DT", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 430, "question": "So we can get a sense of the scale of this, what do you do to commence this rescue operation?", "question_tokens": ["So", "we", "can", "get", "a", "sense", "of", "the", "scale", "of", "this", ",", "what", "do", "you", "do", "to", "commence", "this", "rescue", "operation", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["IN", "PRP", "MD", "VB", "DT", "NN", "IN", "DT", "NN", "IN", "DT", ",", "WP", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", "TO", "VB", "DT", "NN", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 431, "answer": "Well, let me, first of all, go ahead and make a comparison.", "answer_tokens": ["Well", ",", "let", "me", ",", "first", "of", "all", ",", "go", "ahead", "and", "make", "a", "comparison", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110524pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNS", "."], "qSentId": 443, "question": "Are you impressed by the speed of the response?", "question_tokens": ["Are", "you", "impressed", "by", "the", "speed", "of", "the", "response", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VBD", "IN", "DT", "NN", "IN", "DT", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 444, "answer": "Yes.", "answer_tokens": ["Yes", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"LOCATION": ["Oklahoma", "Oklahoma City"]}, "docId": "110524pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "RB", "VBN", "NNS", "WDT", "VBP", "VBN", "JJ", "NNS", "IN", "NNP", ",", "IN", "JJS", "CD", "NNS", "IN", "NNP", "NNP", "."], "qSentId": 469, "question": "What do you think we can expect?", "question_tokens": ["What", "do", "you", "think", "we", "can", "expect", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", "PRP", "MD", "VB", "."], "aSentId": 470, "answer": "Well, we've already seen tornadoes that have dropped big tornadoes across Oklahoma, at least four fatalities near Oklahoma City.", "answer_tokens": ["Well", ",", "we", "'ve", "already", "seen", "tornadoes", "that", "have", "dropped", "big", "tornadoes", "across", "Oklahoma", ",", "at", "least", "four", "fatalities", "near", "Oklahoma", "City", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110524pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNS", ",", "CC", "PRP", "VBP", "NNS", ",", "IN", "DT", "NN", "IN", "DT", ",", "DT", "NN", "IN", "DT", ",", "RB", ",", "PRP", "VBP", ",", "EX", "VBZ", "NN", "CC", "DT", "NN", "VBZ", "PRP", "IN", "."], "qSentId": 525, "question": "I mean, it's just been decimated, hasn't it?", "question_tokens": ["I", "mean", ",", "it", "'s", "just", "been", "decimated", ",", "has", "n't", "it", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", ",", "PRP", "VBZ", "RB", "VBN", "VBN", ",", "VBZ", "RB", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 526, "answer": "Yes, and you know Piers, after an incident like this, a disaster like this, often, you know, there's adrenaline and the adrenaline carries you through.", "answer_tokens": ["Yes", ",", "and", "you", "know", "Piers", ",", "after", "an", "incident", "like", "this", ",", "a", "disaster", "like", "this", ",", "often", ",", "you", "know", ",", "there", "'s", "adrenaline", "and", "the", "adrenaline", "carries", "you", "through", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110524pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNS", ",", "RB", "."], "qSentId": 546, "question": "You think it's irresponsible for President Obama to say that?", "question_tokens": ["You", "think", "it", "'s", "irresponsible", "for", "President", "Obama", "to", "say", "that", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "PRP", "VBZ", "JJ", "IN", "NNP", "NNP", "TO", "VB", "IN", "."], "aSentId": 547, "answer": "Yes, indeed.", "answer_tokens": ["Yes", ",", "indeed", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Obama"]}}]